unlockthegame.com 2016-02-07

# Privacy Statement - Unlock The Game

_**Privacy Policy**_

Unlock The Game recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of www.unlockthegame.com. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website. 

 _ **How Information is Collected  **_

Unlock The Game collects information about users by voluntary submission, IP addresses and cookies. 

No registration is required to enter this website. 

_**Voluntary Submission**_

When users elect to purchase products or subscribe to newsletters users are required to supply certain personal information during the registration process. Information collected through these forms may be used by Unlock The Game to improve the content of our Web pages, gather demographic information about our users in general, for audits and to perform statistical analysis of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our Web site. 

Unlock The Game will not disclose, share, sell or divulge any personal information, such as address, e-mail, telephone and fax numbers, to third parties unless we have informed you, been authorized by you or are required to do so by law. Unlock The Game will maintain this information in accordance with our strict security and confidentiality standards. 

Unlock The Game feels strongly about protecting the privacy of children. No information should be submitted to Unlock The Game by users under the age 18. Children under the age 18 may not register for subscriptions or access those sections of the Web site that require registration. 

_**Agents**_

We employ an agency and a web developer to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending emails, removing repetitive information form customer lists, analyzing data, and providing marketing assistance.  

_**IP Addresses**_

An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you surf the Internet. When you request pages from the Unlock The Game web server, the server automatically logs your IP address, but not the e-mail address. Unlock The Game may use the log for various purposes, including systems administration and to report aggregate information to advertisers. 

_**Opting Out**_

Unlock The Game may periodically send out e-mail newsletters to our users about new services, products or other news using e-mail addresses provided at registration or otherwise. Upon request, Unlock The Game will remove users (and their information) from our database or permit them to "opt-out" of any further e-mail newsletter lists. If you receive any such e-mail messages that you do not wish to receive again in the future, please [contact us](http://www.unlockthegame.com/utility/showPage/index.cfm?objectID=utg,4393).

_**Links**_

This Web may contain links to other Web sites. Unlock The Game is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Inclusion of links to such Web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such Web sites by Unlock The Game . 

_**Security**_

Unlock The Game uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Nonetheless, Unlock The Game does not guarantee the security, accuracy or completeness of any such information or procedures.

_**Changes and Acceptance**_

Unlock The Game reserves the right to change this policy at any time. By using www.unlockthegame.com you signify your agreement with the terms of our privacy statement. Your continued use of the Web site after any changes to this privacy statement signifies your agreement to the changes. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this Web site, you may write to us at the following postal address:

Unlock The Game  
2620 S. Maryland Parkway, Suite #14-801  
Las Vegas, NV 89109  
USA

or

Unlock The Game  
Suite 223, 30 Denison Street  
Sydney, NSW 2022   
Australia
